Guide to the Asian CineVision Records TAM.416
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Video Recordings, 545120
  - The Song of Chaophaya 1 of 5, cuid2575; 545135 (Box 259)
  - The Song of Chaophaya 2 of 5, cuid2576; 545134 (Box 260)
  - The Song of Chaophaya 3 of 5, cuid2577; 545133 (Box 261)
  - The Song of Chaophaya 4 of 5, cuid2578; 545132 (Box 262)
  - The Song of Chaophaya 5 of 5, cuid2579; 545131 (Box 263)
  - Memory of the Soil, cuid2580; 545130 (Box 264)
  - The River Chao Phraya 1 of 5, cuid2581; 545129 (Box 265)
  - The River Chao Phraya 2 of 5, cuid2582; 545128 (Box 266)
  - The River Chao Phraya 3 of 5, cuid2583; 545127 (Box 267)
  - The River Chao Phraya 4 of 5, cuid2584; 545126 (Box 268)
  - The River Chao Phraya 5 of 5, cuid2585; 545125 (Box 269)
  - Laser Man Peter Wang Films (2 reels), cuid2586; 545124 (Box 270)
  - Laser Man Peter Wang Films (3 reels), cuid2587; 545123 (Box 271)
  - May Jane (Parts 4 and 5), cuid2588; 545122 (Box 272)
  - May Jane (Parts 1, 2, and 3 ), cuid2589; 545121 (Box 273)
- Series V: Archived Websites, March 2014-ongoing; cuid2707; 545118; 6 websites in six archived websites.
  Scope and Content Note
  Asian CineVision (ACV) is a non-profit media arts organization that develops, promotes and preserves media made by or about peoples of Asian descent. Asian CineVision was founded by grassroots media activists in New York's Chinatown in 1976 to raise social and cultural awareness of the Asian American experience, both in the Asian American community and among the general public. CineVue Online is ACV's media arts journal established in 1986. The websites contains their media arts journal, information on their Asian American International Film Festival, specifically the 2014-2018 editions of the festival, news listings, event listings, trailers and descriptions of films in the festival, and press releases.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually.
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of aaiff.org and asiancinevision.org in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.